George M. Gray Museum Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- 35mm Slide Collection, Series I
  - People., 002025
    - Peter E. Schwamb. Peter E. Schwamb., Nov 1964; 002544
    - Peter J. Oldham. Peter J. Oldham., Jul 1965; 002498
    - Peter J. Oldham. Peter J. Oldham., Mar 1966; 002497
    - Peter J. Oldham. Peter J. Oldham., May 1965; 002495
    - Peter J. Oldham. Peter J. Oldham., May 1965; 002496
    - Peter J. Oldham. Peter J. Oldham., Nov 1964; 002499
    - Robert H. Parker & J. Stewart Nagle. Robert H. Parker & J. Stewart Nagle., Jan 1965; 002515
    - Robert H. Parker. Robert H. Parker., Aug 1966; 002514
    - Robert H. Parker. Robert H. Parker., Oct 1965; 002516
    - Robert T. Wilce. Robert T. Wilce., Jul 1967; 002630
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002454
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002455
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002456
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002457
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002458
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002459
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002460
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002461
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002462
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002463
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002464
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002465
    - Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Roger H. Green & Katharine D. Hobson. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002466
    - Roger H. Green. Roger H. Green. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002452
    - Roger H. Green. Roger H. Green. Massachusetts: Barnstable., 31 Mar 1967; 002453
    - Ruth Von Arx & Robert H. Parker. Ruth Von Arx & Robert H. Parker., Jul 1965; 002619
    - Ruth Von Arx. Ruth Von Arx., Oct 1964; 002618
    - SEP Meeting. SEP Meeting., Aug 1967; 002665
    - SEP Meeting. SEP Meeting., Aug 1967; 002666
    - SEP Meeting. SEP Meeting., Aug 1967; 002667
    - SEP Meeting. SEP Meeting., Aug 1967; 002668
    - SEP Meeting. SEP Meeting., Aug 1967; 002669
    - SEP Meeting. SEP Meeting., Aug 1967; 002670
    - SEP at Clauson's. SEP at Clauson's., May 1965; 002664
    - Shirley Conover. Shirley Conover., Oct 1965; 002434
    - Stuart L. Santos. Stuart L. Santos., Feb 1966; 002534
    - Stuart L. Santos. Stuart L. Santos., Jun 1966; 002531
    - Stuart L. Santos. Stuart L. Santos., Jun 1966; 002532
    - Stuart L. Santos. Stuart L. Santos., Jun 1966; 002533
    - Stuart L. Santos. Stuart L. Santos., Oct 1965; 002535
    - Susan D. Burns. Susan D. Burns., 002423
    - Victor A. Zullo. Victor A. Zullo., Jun 1967; 002660
    - Victor A. Zullo. Victor A. Zullo., Jun 1967; 002661
    - Victor A. Zullo. Victor A. Zullo., Oct 1965; 002662
    - Victor A. Zullo. Victor A. Zullo., Oct 1965; 002663
    - W. Duane Hope. W. Duane Hope., Aug 1965; 002472
    - W. Duane Hope. W. Duane Hope., Jun 1965; 002473
    - W. Duane Hope. W. Duane Hope., Jun 1965; 002474
    - William C. Summers & Armand Roberge. William C. Summers & Armand Roberge., Feb 1967; 002579
    - William C. Summers, Louise F. Bush & Victor Zullo. William C. Summers, Louise F. Bush & Victor Zullo., Jun 1967; 002615
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002586
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002587
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002588
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002589
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002590
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002591
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002592
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002593
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002594
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002595
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002596
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002597
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002598
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002599
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002600
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002601
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002602
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002603
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002604
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002605
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002606
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002607
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002608
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Feb 1967; 002609
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Jul 1967; 002580
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Jul 1967; 002581
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Jul 1967; 002582
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Jul 1967; 002583
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Jul 1967; 002584
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Jul 1967; 002585
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Jun 1976; 002578
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Mar 1967; 002614
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Sep 1967; 002610
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Sep 1967; 002611
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Sep 1967; 002612
    - William C. Summers. William C. Summers., Sep 1967; 002613
    - William D. Hummon. William D. Hummon., May 1969; 002475
    - William H. Amos. William H. Amos., Aug 1965; 002414
    - William H. Amos. William H. Amos., Aug 1965; 002415
  - Specimens., 003323
    - Acanthodoris pilosa. 35mm Slide Flatholmskar, Gullmarn, Sverige. 28 Nov 1962., 003154
    - Acanthodoris pilosa. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. Nov 1965., 003155
    - Acanthohaustorius intermedius. 35mm Slide Quick's Hole, Elizabeth Islands, MA. 20 Nov. 1963., 003306
    - Acanthohaustorius millsi. 35mm Slide Quick's Hole, Elizabeth Islands, MA. 20 Nov. 1963., 003307
    - Aelodia papillosa. 35mm Slide Gonad y Gyt, Menai Straits, Wales. 10 Apr 1964., 003156
    - Aelodia papillosa. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 03 Dec 1965., 003157
    - Aelodia papillosa. 35mm Slide Oct 1969., 003158
    - Amphinome rostrata. 35mm Slide Aug 1970., 003220
    - Amphinome rostrata. 35mm Slide Aug 1970., 003221
    - Anaperus gardineri. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 30'N, 70D 51'W. 06 Jan 1966., 003117
    - Anaperus gardineri. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 30'N, 70D 51'W. 06 Jan 1966., 003118
    - Ancula gibbosa. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003159
    - Ancula gibbosa. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003160
    - Arctica islandica. 35mm Slide Menemsha Bight, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 21 Mar 1967., 003207
    - Arenicola cristata. 35mm Slide Mar 1967., 003222
    - Arenicola cristata. 35mm Slide Mar 1967., 003223
    - Arenicola cristata. 35mm Slide Mar 1967., 003224
    - Arenicola marina. 35mm Slide Nobska Point, Woods Hole, MA. 23 Jun 1965., 003225
    - Asabellides oculata. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 47.4'N, 70D 26.7' W. 07 Feb 1966., 003226
    - Asychis urceolata. 35mm Slide MBL, Woods Hole, MA. Dec 1962., 003227
    - Autolytus fasciatus. 35mm Slide off Emerson's, Nonamesset Island, MA. 14 Sep 1965., 003228
    - Autolytus fasciatus. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 29 Jun 1966., 003229
    - Autolytus fasciatus. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 29 Jun 1966., 003230
    - Autolytus prolifer. 35mm Slide off Emerson's, Nonamesset Island, MA. 14 Sep 1965., 003231
    - Autolytus prolifer. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 07 Jun 1966., 003232
    - Autolytus prolifer. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 07 Jun 1966., 003233
    - Balanus balanus. 35mm Slide Crab Ledge, Chatham, MA. 30 Sep 1969., 003298
    - Barentsia laxa. 35mm Slide off Nashawena Island, Buzzards Bay, MA. 17 Aug 1965., 003134
    - Barentsia laxa. 35mm Slide off Nashawena Island, Buzzards Bay, MA. 17 Aug 1965., 003135
    - Barentsia laxa. 35mm Slide off Nashawena Island, Buzzards Bay, MA. 17 Aug 1965., 003136
    - Barentsia laxa. 35mm Slide off Nashawena Island, Buzzards Bay, MA. 17 Aug 1965., 003137
    - Boltenia ovifera. 35mm Slide Georges Bank, MA., 003318
    - Boltenia rubra. 35mm Slide Georges Bank, MA. Dec 1962., 003319
    - Botryllus schlosseri. 35mm Slide Park Street, Town landing, Woods Hole, MA. 02 Dec 1967., 003320
    - Botryllus schlosseri. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 02 Aug 1965., 003321
    - Brada villosa. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 31'N, 70D 48.9'W. 30 Jun 1966., 003235
    - Brada villosa. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 31'N, 70D 48.9'W. 30 Jun 1966., 003236
    - Buccinum undatum. 35mm Slide off Chatham, MA. 41D 42.6'N, 69D 47.3' W. 30 Oct 1964., 003142
    - Buccinum undatum. 35mm Slide off Chatham, MA. 41D 42.6'N, 69D 47.3' W. 30 Oct 1964., 003143
    - Buccinum undatum. 35mm Slide Mar 1967., 003144
    - Buccinum undatum. 35mm Slide Mar 1967., 003145
    - Buccinum undatum. 35mm Slide May 1966., 003146
    - Buccinum undatum. 35mm Slide Quoddy Head, Lubec, ME. 18 Aug 1970., 003147
    - Byblis serrata. 35mm Slide Quick's Hole, Elizabeth Islands, MA. 18 Nov. 1963., 003308
    - Cadlina laevis. 35mm Slide Waquoit Bay, MA. 15 Jun 1965., 003161
    - Caecum pulchellum. 35mm Slide, 003234
    - Campanularia flexuosa. 35mm Slide., 003083
    - Catriona aurantia. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Canal, Sandwich, MA. Nov 1965., 003162
    - Catriona aurantia. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Canal, Sandwich, MA. Nov 1965., 003163
    - Catriona aurantia. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Canal, Sandwich, MA. Nov 1965., 003164
    - Centroderes spinosus. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 37' 20"N, 70D 45' 05"W. 29 Jul 1966., 003129
    - Cerastoderma pinnulatum. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 31'N, 70D 47' 15"W. 03 Mar 1967., 003208
    - Cerebratulus lacteus. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA., 003127
    - Ceriantheopsis americanus. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 30'N, 70D 51'W. 30 Jun 1966., 003109
    - Ceriantheopsis americanus. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 30'N, 70D 51'W. 30 Jun 1966., 003110
    - Chaetozone setosa. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Aug 1965., 003237
    - Chlamys islandica. 35mm Slide Tashmoo Pond, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 08 May 1966., 003209
    - Chlamys islandica. 35mm Slide Tashmoo Pond, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 08 May 1966., 003210
    - Chrysaora quinquecirrha. 35mm Slide off Fisheries Jetty, Woods Hole, MA. 27 Aug 1965., 003101
    - Chrysaora quinquecirrha. 35mm Slide off Fisheries Jetty, Woods Hole, MA. 27 Aug 1965., 003102
    - Ciona intestinalis. 35mm Slide, 003322
    - Cirratulus grandis. 35mm Slide Jun 1968., 003238
    - Clava leptostyla. 35mm Slide Beach off Old Sandwich Road, Ellisville, MA. 11 Sep 1967., 003084
    - Clava leptostyla. 35mm Slide Beach off Old Sandwich Road, Ellisville, MA. 11 Sep 1967., 003085
    - Clava leptostyla. 35mm Slide, 003086
    - Colus stimpsoni. 35mm Slide Crab Ledge, Chatham, MA. 30 Sep 1969., 003148
    - Colus stimpsoni. 35mm Slide Crab Ledge, Chatham, MA. 30 Sep 1969., 003149
    - Colus stimpsoni. 35mm Slide Crab Ledge, Chatham, MA. 30 Sep 1969., 003150
    - Corophium acherusicum. 35mm Slide Hadley Harbor, MA. 25 Feb 1964., 003309
    - Corophium tuberculatum. 35mm Slide Quick's Hole, Elizabeth Islands, MA. 23 Dec 1963., 003310
    - Corryphella verrucosa. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003173
    - Corryphella verrucosa. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003174
    - Corryphella verrucosa. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Canal, Sandwich, MA. 23 Oct 1966., 003175
    - Corymarpha pendula. 35mm Slide MBL Sea Table. 31 Jan 1966., 003087
    - Coryphella gracilis. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Canal, MA. 23 Mar 1966., 003165
    - Coryphella gracilis. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Canal, MA. 23 Mar 1966., 003166
    - Coryphella gracilis. 35mm Slide Menemsha Bight, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 08 Nov 1965., 003167
    - Coryphella lineata. 35mm Slide Vattlestraumen, Bergen region, Norge. 05 Dec 1960., 003168
    - Coryphella pellucida. 35mm Slide Straume Bro, Bergen Region, Norge. 13 Nov 1960., 003169
    - Coryphella pellucida. 35mm Slide Quicks Hole, MA. 22 Apr 1965., 003170
    - Coryphella pellucida. 35mm Slide WHOI Dock pile, Woods Hole, MA. 23 Apr 1965., 003171
    - Coryphella salmonacea. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003172
    - Craterolophus convolvulus. 35mm Slide Rye Harbor, NH. 07 Jul 1965., 003103
    - Craterolophus convolvulus. 35mm Slide Rye Harbor, NH. 07 Jul 1965., 003104
    - Craterolophus convolvulus. 35mm Slide Rye Harbor, NH. 07 Jul 1965., 003105
    - Cuthona concinna. 35mm Slide Black Rocks, Menai Straits, Wales. 13 Apr 1964., 003176
    - Cuthona concinna. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003177
    - Cuthona concinna. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003178
    - Cyanea capillata. 35mm Slide Apr 1968., 003106
    - Dendronotus frondosus. 35mm Slide Millbay, Plymouth, Great Britain. 05 Oct 1961., 003179
    - Dendronotus frondosus. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003180
    - Dendronotus frondosus. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003181
    - Diastoma alternatum. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 17 Jul 1965., 003151
    - Diastoma alternatum. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 17 Jul 1965., 003152
    - Diopatra cuprea. 35mm Slide Barnstable Harbor, MA. 23 Jul 1965., 003239
    - Doridella obscura. 35mm Slide Tarpaulin Cove, Naushon Island, MA. 17 Jul 1967, 003182
    - Doridella obscura. 35mm Slide Tarpaulin Cove, Naushon Island, MA. 17 Jul 1967, 003183
    - Doris bifida. 35mm Slide MBL, Woods Hole, MA., 003184
    - Dosima fascicularis. 35mm Slide MBL Beach, Woods Hole, MA. 12 Jul 1965., 003299
    - Dosima fascicularis. 35mm Slide MBL Beach, Woods Hole, MA. 12 Jul 1965., 003300
    - Doto coronata. 35mm Slide Vattlestraumen, Bergen region, Norge. 09 Apr 1960., 003185
    - Doto coronata. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003186
    - Doto formosa. 35mm Slide 1.5 miles from Duck Island Light, CT. 26 May 1967., 003187
    - Echinoderes remanei. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 33' 40"N, 70D 39' 45"W. 17 Aug 1966., 003130
    - Echinoderes sp. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 33' 40"N, 70D 39' 45"W. 17 Aug 1966., 003131
    - Echinoderes sp. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 33' 40"N, 70D 39' 45"W. 17 Aug 1966., 003132
    - Egalvina viridula. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003188
    - Egalvina viridula. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003189
    - Electra pilosa. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 13 May 1966., 003139
    - Elysia catula. 35mm Slide Woods Hole, MA. Jul 1965., 003190
    - Emerita talpoida. 35mm Slide Chappaquoit Beach, Falmouth, MA. 20 Jul 1966., 003314
    - Emerita talpoida. 35mm Slide Chappaquoit Beach, Falmouth, MA. 20 Jul 1966., 003316
    - Eteone trilineata. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 47.4'N, 70D 26.7' W. 07 Feb 1966., 003240
    - Eteone trilineata. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 47.4'N, 70D 26.7' W. 07 Feb 1966., 003241
    - Eteone trilineata. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 47.4'N, 70D 26.7' W. 07 Feb 1966., 003242
    - Eubranchus pallidus. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003191
    - Eubranchus pallidus. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003192
    - Eubranchus pallidus. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003193
    - Eucratea loricata. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003140
    - Eucratea loricata. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003141
    - Eulalia viridis. 35mm Slide off Jobs Neck, Naushon Island, MA. 16 Jun 1965., 003243
    - Eumida sanguinea. 35mm Slide off Jobs Neck, Naushon Island, MA. 16 Jun 1965., 003244
    - Eumida sanguinea. 35mm Slide off Jobs Neck, Naushon Island, MA. 16 Jun 1965., 003245
    - Facelina bostoniensis. 35mm Slide Menemsha Bight, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 08 Nov 1965., 003194
    - Facelina bostoniensis. 35mm Slide Menemsha Bight, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 08 Nov 1965., 003195
    - Facelina bostoniensis. 35mm Slide Menemsha Bight, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 08 Nov 1965., 003196
    - Gonionemus vertens. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Jul 1965., 003088
    - Gonionemus vertens. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Jul 1965., 003089
    - Gonionemus vertens. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Jul 1965., 003090
    - Gonionemus vertens. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Jul 1965., 006530
    - Gonionemus vertens. 35 mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Jul 1965., 006531
    - Gonionemus vertens. 35 mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Jul 1965., 006532
    - Gonionemus vertens. 35 mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Jul 1965., 006533
    - Halcampa duodecimcirrata. 35mm Slide MBL, Woods Hole, MA. Mar 1967., 003111
    - Haliclystus auricula. 35mm Slide Nobska Point, Woods Hole, MA. 05 Apr 1966., 003107
    - Haliclystus auricula. 35mm Slide Nobska Point, Woods Hole, MA. 05 Apr 1966., 003108
    - Haliplanella luciae. 35mm Slide MBL Sea Table. 28 Jan 1966., 003112
    - Haliplanella luciae. 35mm Slide MBL Sea Table. 28 Jan 1966., 003113
    - Haloclava producta. 35mm Slide, 003114
    - Harmothoe imbricata. 35mm Slide Hadley Harbor, MA. 17 Nov 1964., 003246
    - Heteromysis formosa. 35mm Slide East side of Basset's Island, Pocasset, MA. 30 Sep 1965., 003313
    - Hyas coarctatus. 35mm Slide Menemsha Bight, Vineyard Sound, MA. 21 Mar 1967., 003315
    - Hydractinia echinata. 35mm Slide Barnstable Harbor, MA. 26 Jul 1966., 003091
    - Hydractinia echinata. 35mm Slide Barnstable Harbor, MA. 26 Jul 1966., 003092
    - Hydroides dianthus. 35mm Slide MBL, Woods Hole, MA., 003247
    - Laetmonice filicornis. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003248
    - Laetmonice filicornis. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003249
    - Laetmonice filicornis. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003250
    - Lamellidoris fusca. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. Nov 1965., 003197
    - Lamellidoris fusca. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. Nov 1965., 003198
    - Lamellidoris muricata. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 06 Dec 1965., 003199
    - Lepas anatifera. 35mm Slide Garbage Beach, Woods Hole, MA. Aug 1965., 003301
    - Lepas anatifera. 35mm Slide Garbage Beach, Woods Hole, MA. Aug 1965., 003302
    - Lepas anatifera. 35mm Slide, 003303
    - Lepidonotus squamatus. 35mm Slide off Jobs Neck, Naushon Island, MA. 16 Jun 1965., 003251
    - Lepidonotus squamatus. 35mm Slide off Jobs Neck, Naushon Island, MA. 16 Jun 1965., 003252
    - Lepidonotus sublevis. 35mm Slide off Poponessett Beach, MA. 03 Aug 1965., 003253
    - Loligo pealeii. 35mm Slide Aug 1969., 003219
    - Loxosomella nordgaardi. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 56'N, 70D 26' W. 23 Mar 1966., 003138
    - Macoma balthica. 35mm Slide off Menemsha, Vineyard Sound, MA. 03 Mar 1967., 003211
    - Magelona rosea. 35mm Slide Great Harbor, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Aug 1965., 003254
    - Magelona rosea. 35mm Slide Hadley Harbor, MA. 01 Jun 1966., 003255
    - Magelona rosea. 35mm Slide Hadley Harbor, MA. 01 Jun 1966., 003256
    - Maldanopsis elongata. 35mm Slide off Nashawena Island, MA. 30 Jun 1966., 003257
    - Marphysa sanguinea. 35mm Slide off Emerson's, Nonamesset Island, MA. 14 Sep 1965., 003258
    - Marphysa sanguinea. 35mm Slide off Emerson's, Nonamesset Island, MA. 14 Sep 1965., 003259
    - Metridium senile. 35mm Slide Sandwich Jetty, Sandwich, MA. 04 Jun 1965., 003115
    - Metridium senile. 35mm Slide Crab Ledge, Chatham, MA. 30 Sep 1969., 003116
    - Microciona prolifera. 35mm Slide. Toby Island, Monument Beach, MA. Sep 1965., 003080
    - Micrura affinis. 35mm Slide, 003128
    - Monocelis sp. 35mm Slide Aquaculture Lab, Dennis, MA. 10 Sep 1965., 003120
    - Neochildia fusca. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, MA. 41D 30'N, 70D 51'W. 06 Jan 1966., 003119
    - Neochildia fusca. 35mm Slide Aquaculture Lab, Dennis, MA. 23 Jun 1965., 003121
    - Neochildia fusca. 35mm Slide Aquaculture Lab, Dennis, MA. Sep 1965., 003122
    - Nereis pelagica. 35mm Slide off Jobs Neck, Naushon Island, MA. 16 Jun 1965., 003260
    - Nereis pelagica. 35mm Slide off Jobs Neck, Naushon Island, MA. 16 Jun 1965., 003261
    - Nereis pelagica. 35mm Slide off Jobs Neck, Naushon Island, MA. 16 Jun 1965., 003262
    - Nereis pelagica. 35mm Slide off Jobs Neck, Naushon Island, MA. 16 Jun 1965., 003263
    - Nicolea venustula. 35mm Slide Hadley Harbor, MA. 07 Feb 1965., 003264
    - Nicolea venustula. 35mm Slide Hadley Harbor, MA. 07 Feb 1965., 003265
    - Ninoe nigripes. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, off Nasawena Island, MA. 11 Aug 1965., 003266
    - Ninoe nigripes. 35mm Slide Buzzards Bay, off Nasawena Island, MA. 11 Aug 1965., 003267
    - Nucella lapillus. 35mm Slide, 003153
    - Obelia geniculata. 35mm Slide Woods Hole, MA., 003093
    - Paranaitis speciosa. 35mm Slide off Cuttyhunk Island, MA. 30 Jun 1966., 003268
    - Paranaitis speciosa. 35mm Slide off Cuttyhunk Island, MA. 30 Jun 1966., 003269
    - Paranaitis speciosa. 35mm Slide off Cuttyhunk Island, MA. 30 Jun 1966., 003270
    - Paraonis gracilis. 35mm Slide Barnstable Harbor, MA. Aug 1964., 003271
    - Pennaria tiarella. 35mm Slide Hadley Harbor, MA. 07 Jul 1965., 003094
    - Pennaria tiarella. 35mm Slide Hadley Harbor, MA. 07 Jul 1965., 003095
    - Pennaria tiarella. 35mm Slide Hadley Harbor, MA. 07 Jul 1965., 003096
    - Phascolion strombi. 35mm Slide off Gay Head, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 22 Jun 1966, 003296
    - Phascolion strombi. 35mm Slide off Gay Head, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 22 Jun 1966, 003297
    - Phascolopsis gouldii. 35mm Slide Mar 1967., 003295
    - Pherusa affinis. 35mm Slide off Lobsterville Beach, Menemsha Bight, MA. 15 Jul 1965., 003272
    - Phyllodoce arenae. 35mm Slide Eel Pond, Woods Hole, MA. 16 Aug 1965., 003273
    - Phyllodoce mucosa. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 47.4'N, 70D 26.7'W. 07 Feb 1966., 003274
    - Phyllodoce mucosa. 35mm Slide Cape Cod Bay, MA. 41D 47.4'N, 70D 26.7'W. 07 Feb 1966., 003275
    - Pinnixa chaetopterana. 35mm Slide Tashmoo Pond, Martha's Vineyard, MA. 08 May 1966., 003317
    - Placopecten magellanicus. 35mm Slide Menemsha Bight, Vineyard Sound, MA. 23 Jan 1967., 003212
    - Placopecten magellanicus. 35mm Slide Menemsha Bight, Vineyard Sound, MA. 23 Jan 1967., 003213
    - Placopecten magellanicus. 35mm Slide Mar 1967., 003214
    - Placopecten magellanicus. 35mm Slide Mar 1967., 003215
    - Placopecten magellanicus. 35mm Slide Mar 1967., 003216